Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jcboyanton (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Sales

Business Development Complex Sales

JC Boyanton

SVP, Technology Banking at SunTrust now Truist Atlanta, Georgia

Summary

Through SunTrust now Truist's unique OneTeam approach, JC provides comprehensive financial services to emerging-growth and middle market companies in the technology industry.

JC has over 20 years experience advising companies ranging from start-ups to the Fortune 500 and has executed on broad range of transactions including cash flow, asset-based, and venture debt financings, syndicated loans, mezzanine, private equity, and mergers and acquisitions advisory services.

Experience

Truist

Senior Vice President, Middle Market Banking December 2019 - Present (8 months)

SunTrust Bank

Senior Vice President, Commercial Banking January 2013 - December 2019 (7 years)

PNC

Vice President, Corporate & Institutional Banking April 2012 - January 2013 (10 months)

PNC acquired RBC Bank USA

RBC Bank

Senior Relationship Manager, Corporate Banking - Knowledge Based Industries

December 2009 - March 2012 (2 years 4 months)

Senior relationship manager to high-growth technology companies and venture/private equity funds. Originated, structured, and executed financing transactions to support growth, recapitalizations, and M&A. Managed venture and private equity sponsor coverage. Advised clients on capital structure and non-bank lending solutions.

Silicon Valley Bank

Vice President

September 2004 - February 2009 (4 years 6 months)

Senior member of relationship management team with global venture bank. Originated, structured, and executed financing transactions for early and growth-stage, venture/private equity sponsored, and public technology and life science companies.

Knightsbridge Group, Inc.

Principal

November 2002 - August 2004 (1 year 10 months)

Investment banker providing corporate finance advisory services to the financial services industry.

T. Stephen Johnson & Associates

Vice President

July 1999 - October 2002 (3 years 4 months)

Investment banker focused on the financial services industry. Advised CEOs and boards on the formation of 17 start-up banks and authored business plans and financial models used to raise \$151 million in equity. Executed sell-side M&A assignments, corporate reorganizations, and raised capital for banks through Bear Stearns' trust preferred securities pooling program.

Sumitomo Bank

Corporate Banking Officer

June 1998 - June 1999 (1 year 1 month)

Originated and executed corporate and investment banking transactions for Fortune 500 companies.

AmTrade International Bank Loan Officer/Credit Analyst

May 1996 - May 1998 (2 years 1 month)

Education

The University of Alabama

Bachelor of Science in Commerce and Business Administration, Finance